My mom's so funny. She lives in the
South, too. She's still determined to
keep me up-to-date with everybody that I
grew up with, and she'll remind me about
them till the point where I care again.
So, she'll call me up. SHE'S LIKE, "HEY,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?" I'M LIKE, "What's
3:00 in the afternoon, cougar? I'm
working."
And she's like, "But you remember Ashley
Davidson?" I'm like, "No, I don't know
who that is." "Oh, you know who that
is."
Like I was just lying the second before.
"ASHLEY
DAVIDSON! SHE HAD LONG DARK HAIR. She's
on the cheerleading squad." I'm like,
"No, Mom, it still does not RING A
BELL."
"ASHLEY DAVIDSON!"
"HER MOM, ALICE, USED TO CUT YOUR HAIR."
And I'm like, "Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I think I know who that is."
"Well, she's dead."
I'm like, "WHY WOULD YOU CALL TO TELL ME
THAT?" SHE'S LIKE, "CUZ I THOUGHT YOU'D
WANT TO KNOW." I'M LIKE, "I don't even
know who that is." "Oh, you know who
that is."